Advisory Neighborhood Commissions (ANCs) of Washington, D.C. Web Archive dcpl_web002
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Advisory Neighborhood Commissions (ANCs) of Washington, D.C. Web Archive
1988-2018
DCPL Special Collections - MLK Library
Advisory Neighborhood Commissions (ANCs) of Washington, D.C.
dcpl_web002
33 Web Sites Captured
General
A collection of websites documenting the activities of Washington, DC's Advisory Neighborhood Commissions (ANCs).
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
This collection is comprised of dynamic snapshots of sites as they existed at a specific moment, or moments, in time, and should not be confused with current versions of the sites depicted. Due to limitations in web crawling technology, certain page elements may not display as originally intended. This is normal, and we are constantly working to improve capture quality.
- anc | Advisory Neighborhood Commissions, 2017; 939 Captures
  General
  D.C. Government homepage for the city's network of Advisory Neighborhood commissions.
  Acquisition of Web Archives with Archive-It
  Web crawling is managed through the Internet Archive's Archive-It service. This page includes links to both DCPL's collection and the Internet Archive's public collection.
  Crawling is performed periodically by DCPL.
  Access to WARC Files
  Researchers interested in data analysis with web archives may request a WARC file. WARC files are very large and difficult to work with. Your request may take time to process, and we may be unable to deliver your request remotely. Please consult an archivist if you are interested in advanced research with web archives.
  Web Archives from General Internet Archive Collections
  This data is not held by DC Public Library, but within the Internet Archive's collections. The DC Public Library web archiving program has contributed to the Internet Archive's collections since 2016, but has no control over their acquisition processes.
- ANC 1A Home, 2008-2017; 61 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Park View and Columbia Heights neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC-1B - Keeping You Up to Date In Your NeighborhoodWelcome to ANC 1B - ANC-1B, 2003-2017; 211 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the U Street Corridor, Shaw, Pleasant Plains, LeDroit Park, and Columbia Heights neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 1C, 2000-2017; 312 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Adams Morgan neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- ANC1D, 2004-2017; 144 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Mount Pleasant neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 2A, 2010-2017; 112 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the West End and Foggy Bottom neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- Dupont Circle ANC 2B | Washington, DC's best place to live, work and play!, 1988-2017; 289 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Dupont Circle neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 2C, 2013-2017; 44 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Penn Quarter, Downtown, and Chinatown neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 2D, 2012-2017; 60 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Sheridan-Kalorama neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 2E, 2004-2017; 212 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Burleith and Georgetown neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 2F, 2003-2017; 444 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Downtown, Shaw, and Logan Circle neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC3B | Serving Glover Park and Cathedral Heights | Washington DC, 2011-2017; 124 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Cathedral Heights and Glover Park neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 3C, 2006-2017; 112 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Woodley Park, McLean Gardens, Massachusetts Heights, Woodland-Normanstone Terrace, Cleveland Park, and Cathedral Heights neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- Home - Advisory Neighborhood Commission 3D, 2011-2017; 558 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Wesley Heights, Spring Valley, Palisades, The, Kent, Foxhall, and American University Park neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC3E, 2017; 238 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Friendship Heights, Tenleytown, and American University Park neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 3F, 2015-2017; 114 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Forest Hills, Wakefield, and North Cleveland Park neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission, 2005-2017; 94 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Chevy Chase neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 4A Home, 2011-2017; 93 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Shepherd Park, Brightwood, 16th Street Heights, Crestwood, and Colonial Village neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 4B, 2006-2017; 66 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Takoma Park, Riggs Park, Manor Park, Lamond Riggs, and Brightwood neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 4C, 2015-2017; 99 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the 16th Street Heights, Petworth, and Columbia Heights neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 4D, 2015-2017; 58 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Petworth and Brightwood neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 5A, 2010-2017; 95 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Woodridge, Queens Chapel, North Michigan Park, Michigan Park, Lamond Riggs, and Fort Lincoln neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 5B Home, 2015-2016; 34 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Brookland, Michigan Park, North Michigan Park, Queens Chapel, and Woodridge neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 5C | Advisory Neighborhood Commission 5C, 2013-2016; 36 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Woodridge, Langdon, Gateway, Fort Lincoln, Brentwood, and Arboretum neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 5D | ANC 5D represents the Washington, D.C. neighborhoods of Carver-Langston, Ivy City and Trinidad., 2013-2016; 57 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Ivy City, Gallaudet, Trinidad, and Carver Langston neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission 6A, 2016-2017; 183 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Capitol Hill neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission 6B | Serving Capitol Hill / South East, 2013-2017; 138 Captures
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission 6C, 2009-2017; 146 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the NoMa/Sursum Corda, and Near Northeast neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 6D, 2009-2017; 85 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Navy Yard neighborhood of Washington, D.C.
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission 6E | Proudly Representing the Neighborhoods of Mount Vernon Square, NW One, Shaw, and a wee part of Truxton Circle!, 2011-2016; 67 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Truxton Circle, Shaw, and Mount Vernon Square neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 7D Home, 2009-2016; 27 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the River Terrace, Mayfair, Marshall Heights, Kingman Park, Kenilworth, and Eastland Gardens neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- Advisory Neighborhood Commission 7E - Home of the ANC 7E Online Community, 2015-2016; 35 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Marshall Heights, Capitol View, and Benning Heights neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.
- ANC 8A, 2013-2016; 42 Captures
  Website for ANC covering the Fairlawn and Anacostia neighborhoods of Washington, D.C.